<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Books on David Mullet</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/books/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Books on David Mullet</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/books/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Books: &#39;The Woman in the Water&#39;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/books-the-woman-in-the-water/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/books-the-woman-in-the-water/</guid>
      <description>Books: &amp;ldquo;The Woman in the Water&amp;rdquo; I recently finished reading The Woman in the Water by Charles Finch.&#xA;This is a prequel to the popular Charles Lenox mystery series, set in Victorian London. I had read the first in the series, A Beautiful Blue Death, a few years ago and enjoyed it.&#xA;The Woman in the Water is set many years earlier than other books in the series, in 1850. 23-year-old Charles Lenox has recently moved to London with his valet, Graham, with hopes of becoming a private detective.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Currently Reading</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/currently-reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/currently-reading/</guid>
      <description>Currently Reading Leave the Gun, Take the Cannoli by Mark Seal System Collapse by Martha Wells </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Books: &#39;The Ghosts of Rome&#39;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/books-the-ghosts-of-rome/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/books-the-ghosts-of-rome/</guid>
      <description>Books: &amp;ldquo;The Ghosts of Rome&amp;rdquo; I recently finished reading The Ghosts of Rome by Joseph O&amp;rsquo;Connor.&#xA;This is the sequel to 2023&amp;rsquo;s My Father&amp;rsquo;s House, continuing the story of the Rome Escape Line, which helped escaped POWs remain in hiding or safely flee Italy altogether. Most of the major characters from the first book return in this one, but while the first book revolved around Monsignor Hugh O&amp;rsquo;Flaherty, this book revolves more around another of O&amp;rsquo;Flaherty&amp;rsquo;s Escape Line cohorts (aka &amp;lsquo;The Choir&amp;rsquo;), Contessa Giovanna &amp;lsquo;Jo&amp;rsquo; Landini&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Books: &#39;The Last Manager&#39;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/books-the-last-manager/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/books-the-last-manager/</guid>
      <description>Books: &amp;ldquo;The Last Manager: How Earl Weaver Tricked, Tormented, and Reinvented Baseball&amp;rdquo; I recently finished reading The Last Manager: How Earl Weaver Tricked, Tormented, and Reinvented Baseball* by John W. Miller.&#xA;Long time Baltimore Orioles’ manager Earl Weaver is best remembered as a feisty, larger-than-life (but smaller than most men) character, going literally toe-to-toe with MLB umpires in legendary rants that fans loved and journalists loved to write about.&#xA;But this chain-smoking, hard-drinking, foul-mouthed cartoon character was also a Baseball genius ahead of his time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Books: &#39;Precipice&#39;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/books-precipice/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/books-precipice/</guid>
      <description>Books: &amp;ldquo;Precipice&amp;rdquo; I recently finished reading Precipice by Robert Harris.&#xA;I have read several of Harris&amp;rsquo; novels, including The Fear Index, Second Sleep, An Officer and a Spy, and Conclave, which was recently made into an Oscar-nominated movie.&#xA;Like An Officer and a Spy, which was about the Dreyfus Affair, Precipice is a work of fiction based on actual historical events.&#xA;Read on Medium&amp;hellip;&#xA;Read on Substack&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Books: &#39;The Drowned&#39;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/books-the-drowned/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/books-the-drowned/</guid>
      <description>Books: &amp;ldquo;The Drowned&amp;rdquo; I just finished reading The Drowned by John Banville.&#xA;This is the latest in the series of Irish mystery novels featuring Dublin pathologist Quirke and police inspector Strafford. Banville’s first seven Quirke novels were published under the pseudonym Benjamin Black. Some of these earlier stories, such as Christine Falls, were made into movies starring Gabriel Byrne.&#xA;Read on Medium&amp;hellip;&#xA;Read on Substack&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How One Gamer Fell in Love with Reading</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-one-gamer-fell-in-love-with-reading/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-one-gamer-fell-in-love-with-reading/</guid>
      <description>How One Gamer Fell in Love with Reading Kevin was &amp;ldquo;addicted to playing games for about 4 years&amp;rdquo;. He writes about his failed attempts to replace gaming with reading, and what ultimately worked for him. Eventually, he found himself falling in love with reading and wanting to read even more. And he provides tips on how you might &amp;ldquo;replace a habit like gaming with something more productive&amp;rdquo;.&#xA;Read Kevin’s story here.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Books: &#39;The Unpleasantness at the Bellona Club&#39;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/books-the-unpleasantness-at-the-bellona-club/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/books-the-unpleasantness-at-the-bellona-club/</guid>
      <description>Books: &amp;ldquo;The Unpleasantness at the Bellona Club&amp;rdquo; I recently finished reading The Unpleasantness at the Bellona Club by Dorothy L. Sayers. Published in 1928, this is the fifth book featuring Sayers&amp;rsquo; famous amateur detective Lord Peter Wimsey. Martin Edwards makes many mentions of Ayers in his history of mystery writing, The Life of Crime, which I recently enjoyed. So I thought I should at least give it a go.&#xA;Read more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Books: &#39;The Life of Crime&#39; by Martin Edwards</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/books-the-life-of-crime/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/books-the-life-of-crime/</guid>
      <description>Books: &amp;lsquo;The Life of Crime&amp;rsquo; by Martin Edwards I just finished reading The Life of Crime: Detecting the History of Mysteries and their Creators by Martin Edwards.&#xA;This 2022 release is a 622-page comprehensive history of mystery writing, from the eighteenth century to the present. Each chapter contains numerous footnotes, and the book includes a bibliography and two indexes at the back: an Index of Titles and an Index of Names.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Books: &#39;Karla&#39;s Choice&#39;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/books-karlas-choice/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/books-karlas-choice/</guid>
      <description>Books: &amp;lsquo;Karla&amp;rsquo;s Choice&amp;rsquo; by Nick Harkaway I just finished reading Karla&amp;rsquo;s Choice by Nick Harkaway.&#xA;The cover identifies this as &amp;ldquo;A John Le Carré Novel&amp;rdquo;, though Le Carré — who passed away in 2020 — did not write it. Harkaway, an established novelist in his own right, is also the son of the late spy novelist John Le Carré. Karla&amp;rsquo;s Choice is set in the world of British agent George Smiley — the world that Le Carré created — and slots in between The Spy Who Came in from the Cold (1963) and The Looking Glass War (1965).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Books: &#39;Broken Trust: A Spenser Novel&#39;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/books-broken-trust/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/books-broken-trust/</guid>
      <description>Books: &amp;lsquo;Broken Trust: A Spenser Novel&amp;rsquo; by Mike Lupica I recently finished reading Broken Trust by Mike Lupica, the 50th title in the Spenser series. A little background…&#xA;Robert B. Parker created Boston private detective Spenser (&amp;ldquo;no first name&amp;rdquo;) in 1973 with The Godwulf Manuscript and continued through Sixkill, published posthumously in 2011. Sixkill was the 39th Spenser novel. Along the way (1985–1988), there was a Spenser: For Hire TV series starring Robert Urich.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Books: &#39;The Wrong Hands&#39; by Mark Billingham</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/books-the-wrong-hands/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/books-the-wrong-hands/</guid>
      <description>Books: &amp;lsquo;The Wrong Hands&amp;rsquo; by Mark Billingham I was browsing the New Releases shelves at one of my local libraries (we have library cards for three local systems) when I stumbled upon The Wrong Hands by Mark Billingham. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t familiar with this British author but he has a long-running series of books featuring an inspector Tom Thorne.&#xA;The Wrong Hands is the second book in a different series featuring detective Declan Miller.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Books: &#39;Blood Curse&#39; by Maurizio de Giovanni</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/books-blood-curse/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/books-blood-curse/</guid>
      <description>Books: &amp;lsquo;Blood Curse&amp;rsquo; by Maurizio de Giovanni I just finished reading Blood Curse: The Springtime of Commissario Ricciardi by Maurizio de Giovanni.&#xA;This is the second book in the Commissario Ricciardi mystery series, set in Naples in the 1930s. The series was written and initially published in Italian, but I read the English translation by Antony Shugaar.&#xA;Read more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Books: &#39;The Siege&#39; by Ben Macintyre</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/books-the-siege/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/books-the-siege/</guid>
      <description>Books: &amp;lsquo;The Siege&amp;rsquo; by Ben Macintyre I just finished reading The Siege: A Six-Day Hostage Crisis and the Daring Special-Forces Operation That Shocked the World by Ben Macintyre.&#xA;In 1980, Iranian rebels attacked the Iranian embassy in London, taking more than two dozen hostages and threatening to kill them all if police attempted to enter&amp;hellip;&#xA;Read more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Intelligence. For Dummies.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/artificial-intelligence-for-dummies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/artificial-intelligence-for-dummies/</guid>
      <description>Artificial Intelligence. For Dummies. I see that my local public library has added the following book:&#xA;Artificial Intelligence for Dummies&#xA;I don’t plan to read it; I just found the title interesting.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Books: &#39;The Why is Everything&#39; by Michael Silver</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/books-the-why-is-everything/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/books-the-why-is-everything/</guid>
      <description>Books: &amp;lsquo;The Why Is Everything: A Story of Football, Rivalry, and Revolution&amp;rsquo; by Michael Silver I just finished reading The Why Is Everything: A Story of Football, Rivalry, and Revolution by Michael Silver.&#xA;Silver is a sportswriter currently writing for The Athletic and has previously written for Sports Illustrated and the San Francisco Chronicle, among others.&#xA;In The Why Is Everything, Silver documents the rise of a young generation of NFL coaches, many of whom started or developed under long-time NFL head coach Mike Shanahan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Books: &#39;Safe Houses&#39; by Dan Fesperman</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/books-safe-houses/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/books-safe-houses/</guid>
      <description>Books: &amp;lsquo;Safe Houses&amp;rsquo; by Dan Fesperman In another post, I mentioned that most main characters in espionage stories are either professional spies or unwitting amateurs. That article highlighted the failed professionals of Mick Herron&amp;rsquo;s Slow Horses / Slough House series, who fall somewhat in between.&#xA;In Dan Fesperman&amp;rsquo;s Safe Houses, Helen Abell falls into this gap, as well, but from a different angle. Helen works on the fringe of the espionage business, managing safe houses for the CIA in 1979 Berlin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Slow Horses of Slough House</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-slow-horses-of-slough-house/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-slow-horses-of-slough-house/</guid>
      <description>The Slow Horses of Slough House Many espionage stories&amp;rsquo; protagonists fall into one of two categories&amp;hellip;&#xA;The first category is the espionage professional: Ian Fleming&amp;rsquo;s James Bond, Daniel Silva&amp;rsquo;s Gabriel Allon, and John LeCarre&amp;rsquo;s George Smiley all come to mind. Cool, calm, collected, they are trained and paid to do their nation&amp;rsquo;s dirty work.&#xA;At the other end of the spectrum is the unwitting amateur that finds themselves thrust into a situation which they are seemingly ill-equipped to deal with.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Books: &#39;How We Got to Now: Six Innovations That Made the Modern World&#39; by Steven Johnson</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/books-how-we-got-to-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/books-how-we-got-to-now/</guid>
      <description>Books: &amp;lsquo;How We Got to Now: Six Innovations That Made the Modern World&amp;rsquo; by Steven Johnson I just finished reading How We Got to Now: Six Innovations That Made the Modern World by Steven Johnson, and I enjoyed it quite a bit.&#xA;Goodreads rates it at 4.11 and I would say that is about right, if you enjoy history and science.&#xA;Read more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Book Discovery Resources</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/book-discovery-resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/book-discovery-resources/</guid>
      <description>Book Discovery Resources Here, fellow booklovers, are a few online resources to help you discover your next great read, whether through targeted selection or serendipity. Enjoy!&#xA;Read more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Books: &#39;Bad Debts&#39; by Peter Temple</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/books-bad-debts-by-peter-temple/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/books-bad-debts-by-peter-temple/</guid>
      <description>Books: &amp;lsquo;Bad Debts&amp;rsquo; by Peter Temple I first stumbled across Jack Irish on Acorn TV. It was (or should I say &amp;lsquo;is&amp;rsquo;, in today&amp;rsquo;s perpetual-life-via-streaming world?) an Australian TV series (and movies) starring Guy Pearce (LA Confidential, Memento, The King&amp;rsquo;s Speech). I enjoyed the TV series very much and recently sought out Peter Temple&amp;rsquo;s novels, on which the TV series is based.&#xA;Read more&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
