<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Crime Fiction on David Mullet</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/crime-fiction/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Crime Fiction on David Mullet</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/crime-fiction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Books: Break In</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/books-break-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/books-break-in/</guid>
      <description>Books: Break In I recently decided to revisit the mysteries of Dick Francis, many of which I had read in the 1990s, and found Break In at my local library. I remembered none of the details from my first reading so the story was essentially new to me.&#xA;This is the first of two novels featuring English horse-racing jockey Kit Fielding, with the second book being Bolt. One thing I do recall liking about Francis’ stories is the insights they provided into various professions&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Books: Return to Sender</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/books-return-to-sender/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/books-return-to-sender/</guid>
      <description>Books: Return to Sender I recently finished reading Return to Sender, the latest entry in Craig Johnson&amp;rsquo;s long-running Walt Longmire mystery series, which was the basis for the popular Netflix series from a few years ago.&#xA;After a couple flashback stories—First Frost and Tooth and Claw—the narrative returns to present day Wyoming, picking up where 2023&amp;rsquo;s The Longmire Defense left off. Sheriff Walt Longmire has been asked by a friend to investigate the disappearance of a mail carrier who failed to return from her 300-mile daily delivery route through southern Wyoming’s Red Desert&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Books: Andrea Camilleri&#39;s Inspector Montalbano</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/books-andrea-camilleri-inspector-montalbano/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/books-andrea-camilleri-inspector-montalbano/</guid>
      <description>Books: Andrea Camilleri&amp;rsquo;s Inspector Montalbano Today I stumbled across Flaminia&amp;rsquo;s article from 2023 that looks at Sicilian author Andrea Camilleri and his popular Inspector Montalbano novels. I discovered these a couple years ago via my local library and am really enjoying them.&#xA;On the Writer Who Created His Own Language</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Books: The Amateur</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/books-the-amateur/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/books-the-amateur/</guid>
      <description>Books: The Amateur The Amateur is a 1980 novel by Robert Littel, author of The Company and other espionage novels. It is the basis for the 2025 film of the same name. I haven&amp;rsquo;t watched the movie but I&amp;rsquo;m sure the book was better, since it almost always is, right?&#xA;Berlin, 1972. Charlie Heller&amp;rsquo;s fiancee, Sarah, is taken hostage and murdered by terrorists. Heller works for the CIA&amp;ndash;not as a field agent but rather as an analyst who decrypts confidential intercepted messages&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Books: The Devils Cave</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/books-the-devils-cave/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/books-the-devils-cave/</guid>
      <description>Books: The Devils Cave The Devil&amp;rsquo;s Cave is the fifth book in the Bruno, Chief of Police mystery series by Martin Walker. The stories revolve around the fictional village of St. Denis in southwest France, where Benoît &amp;ldquo;Bruno&amp;rdquo; Courrèges has been the local police chief for the past ten years or so&amp;hellip;&#xA;Read on Medium&amp;hellip;&#xA;Read on Substack&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Crime Fiction - Recent Reads</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/crime-fiction-recent-reads/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/crime-fiction-recent-reads/</guid>
      <description>Crime Fiction - Recent Reads I love good crime fiction, and I&amp;rsquo;ve been feasting on a variety of it in recent weeks. Here&amp;rsquo;s a brief roundup&amp;hellip;&#xA;Read on Substack&amp;hellip;&#xA;Read on Medium&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
